I was surprised.
びっくりした
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
I was surprised.
び っくりした
Ah, I was surprised.
あ、びっくりした
Is it okay to remove the tower?
タワーを抜くことっていい?
It's okay, Tower.
大丈夫だよ、タワー
Yeah.
うん
I can wash it.
洗えてます
Can you wash here too?
ここも洗えてる?
I washed it.
洗いましたよ
Properly?
ちゃんと?
Are you washing it properly?
ちゃんと洗ってる?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I'm sweating, so I prepared a bath.
じゃあ、汗かいちゃったから、 お風呂用意したんで、
You can come in.
入ってもいいよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめん
I got the temperature wrong.
温度間違えちゃった
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめん
I got the temperature wrong.
温度間違えちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I got the temperature wrong.
温度間違えちゃった
Can I talk to you?
話 していいの?
Something like
みたいな感じで
difference.
さ
I got the temperature wrong.
温 度間違えちゃった
温 度 間 違 え ちゃ った
I got the temperature wrong.
温度間違えちゃった
a,
あ、
It's hot.
暑 いね
It was too hot.
暑すぎた
It was hot.
暑かった